# 哈喽大家好
Hello, everyone
# 今天是父亲节
Today is Father’s Day
# 带我老爸到杭州去玩一下
Bringing my dad to have fun in Hangzhou
# 然后把我女儿也带上
And my daughter, too
# 这样才能显示出我也在过节
In this way, you know I’m celebrating as well
# 现在我们就开车到机场
Now, we are driving to the airport
# 走嘛
Let’s go
# 沺沺和爸爸一起出去玩开心吗
Tiantian, are you happy going out with dad?
# 开心
Happy
# 今天杭州西湖这里下很大的雨
It’s raining hard at West Lake, Hangzhou today
# 所以我们今天只能说买把伞走一走就算了
So we are just buying an umbrella and having a walk today
# 是不是宝贝
Isn’t it, babe?
# 下雨不是特别好
Raining is not good
# 到处都是水对不对
Water is everywhere, right?
# 而且还起风有点冷
And it also feels a bit cold with the wind blowing
# 我们四川要热得多
It's much warmer in Sichuan
# 所以带孩子和老爸到这里来逛一圈
So, we are just having a walk here
# 走嘛
Let’s go
# 这边的柳树很漂亮对吧
These willows are pretty，right?
# 对
Yeah
# 这边还有桃树
There are peach trees as well
# 待会带你去吃西湖醋鱼好不好
I will take you to have West Lake vinegar fish later, yeah?
# 喜欢吃吗
Do you like it?
# 它以为你有东西喂它
It thought you have something to feed it
# 来
Come
# 丢 再丢
Throw, a bit more
# 它走啦
It’s gone
# 不可以踩小草快出来
You can’t step on the lawn
# 你走一会吧好不好 爸爸牵
Can you walk a little? Daddy will be holding your hand
# 虽然今天天气不怎么好
Although the weather is not that good
# 但是还是来玩一趟嘛
But we are having a trip
# 来都来了一千多公里是吧
We are already here, traveled more than 1000Km
# 还是来逛一圈下大雨也要来逛一圈
So we're still having a walk even it’s raining right now
# 上二楼在哪里
Where is the second floor?
# 二楼这边上
This way please
# 头发都散了
Your hair is all loose
# 哈喽 大家好
Hello everyone
# 本来是说这两天带我老爸和女儿到西湖玩一下
We have planned to take my father and daughter have a trip to West Lake
# 结果这两天在下雨
But it is always raining these days
# 所以正好到这边去拜访一个朋友 一个老师
So we are going to visit one of my friend, a master
# 你们猜一下是谁 跟他学习学习
Guess who it is, we are going to learn from him
# 现在我们在这个工业园区这里 走吧
Now we are in the industrial park, let’s go
# 哈喽
Hello
# 哈喽哈喽
Hello, Hello
# 你好你好
Hi
# 王老师好王老师好
Hi, Chef Wang
# 哈喽哈喽 你们好
Hello, everyone
# 来吧来吧
Come on
# 全员迎接
Full team greeting
# 我们公司人比较多
We have a lot of people here
# 比我们工作室要大很多倍
The studio is many times larger than ours
# 是吗
Is it?
# 对 我们总共才十多台电脑
Yeah, we only have a dozen computers in total
# 这才只是1号
This is just the first one
# 我们这边直播 直播平时我们在这边播
This is where we do live-streaming
# 来 宝贝
Come on babe
# 看一下 你平时只要这边机位开起来以后你只要坐下
Have a look, you can just sit here when you start filming
# 然后你看这边全部就能看到你自己的情况
And you can have a clear sight of yourself here
# 然后下面大家刷什么弹幕啊 互动 然后你的销售额什么
And the chat, interactions, and your sales
# 都可以直接第二个屏幕显示
All of these are displayed on the second screen
# 所以你可以坐下来感受感受
You can sit down and have a feel
# 然后这是麦克风 你说话的话可以感觉一下
And this is the microphone, you can have a feel
# 这个太牛了这个
This is decent
# 给你们点赞 这个真的太牛了
I will give a thumb up for this, this is insane!
# 这个声音是不是很带劲
Sounds exciting, right?
# 嗯 这边就是平时切换啊 导播 要做一个渐影
If you want to switch the contents, or make a fading effect
# 做什么效果都可以用一个人来控
Any animations can be controlled by one person
# 然后这边是声音 声控
And here is the volume control
# 全部都自动对焦
It's autofocus
# 然后这是电影机的画质 其实也不重
And this gives you the film-level image quality. And it's not heavy
# 体验一下
Have a feel
# 诶 不重
No, it’s not heavy
# 不重不重 挺轻的
Yeah, it’s pretty light
# 没有我想象中的重
It’s not as heavy as I thought
# 你们现在是用什么在拍 还是用索尼的
What are you guys filming with? Are you still using SONY?
# A73 就是我们手里的那台A73
SONY A7iii, the one we are using right now
# 主力机现在
It’ our primary one
# 可以可以 A73够了
Yeah, A7iii is enough
# 我们这边其实是
This is our server room
# 服务器
Server
# 对 我们公司其实所有的人都可以进入这个主服务器
Yeah, all our employees have access to this server
# 然后服务器的速度非常快 读写都是一个GB一秒
And this server is super-fast. The I/O speed is 1GB/s
# 每个人的电脑可以同时访问同样的素材 可以多个人同时做同一个视频
Everyone’s computer can access the same material at the same time and work on the same video.
# 看一下 我们这儿奇奇怪怪的屏幕非常多
Have a look, we have a lot of odd screens
# 特别特别长的 超长的
This one is very very long
# 5k屏
5K screen
# 动画师 他就是专门负责做我们的动画
He is the animator. He specializes in our animation production
# 然后我们这边的动画都是他一个人
And he’s the only one who is making animation
# 你们现在剪片都是用什么在剪
What are you guys using for video editing?
# pr
Premiere
# 其实用达芬奇可能更带劲一点
DaVinci Resolve might work better
# 这是辣椒面
This is chili flakes
# 从我们老家带过来的
We brought it from our hometown
# 谢谢 谢谢
Thank you
# 你们的大礼包对吧 多谢多谢
Your gift pack, right? Thank you
# 这个东西也是和这个一样功能的导播台
This broadcast station has the same functions as the other one
# 但它的优点就是它是同时把3张摄影卡的信号聚到一起推流出去
But it has the feature of combining signals from three filming cards and pushing the stream at the same time
# 这样就不会卡 你在任何地方都可以播
And it will not be lagging, so you can stream anywhere you want
# 我看看手感
Let me try it
# 挺重的 有一斤
It’s a bit heavy, about 1 jin (500g)
# TS80 然后这你们到时候装在相机或者那个边上
TS80 and you can put it on the camera or by the side
# 然后只要把相机信号接上就可以直接播了
And connect the camera signal, then you can start streaming
# 然后这样推出去的信号也是好的
The signal is great, too
# 不会有什么问题
There won’t be any issues
# 潘老师又解决我们第一个大难题 直播的问题
Pan Laoshi has solved another big problem for us, a live streaming problem
("Laoshi": honorific)
# 直播老是卡
Our live streaming is always lagging
# 那我们还是想看一下潘老师的red
I still want to see Pan Laoshi's red
# red拍起来质感就不一样了
The image quality of red is phenomenal
# 这个画质就真的绝了
The image quality is decent
# 拍出来就不一样 然后
It makes such a difference, and...
# 这个焦没对上
The camera is not focusing
# 对 给你拿下来 可以直接拿着用
This can be taken off and used directly
# 这个重量
This weight
# 其实也还好吧
It’s actually alright
# 比c500重一点点吧 比c500可能重个一两斤
A bit heavier than c500, probably 1-2 jin (0.5kg-1kg) heavier
# 可以看比如我坐在这里
And, say I'm sitting here
# 然后它这个主要是都是触摸屏的
And it’s all touch-screen
# 还是触摸屏的
Touch-screen?
# 对 所以调起来就特别特别方便
Yeah, so it’s more convenient to adjust
# 比如说这边按了以后
For example, if you touched here
# 这个应该有六七斤吧
This should be about 6-7 jin (3kg-3.5kg)
# 但这个确实画质看起来很厉害
But the image quality is fabulous
# 这个画质还是感觉又有点不一样
This image quality feels a bit different
# 确实red就有最好的视觉上的感觉和画质
Indeed, red has the best image quality and visual feeling
# 这个我比较喜欢 这个就是很老式的
I like this one, this is very old-fashioned
# 电影放映机
Film projector
# 也是特别老的放胶片的
And it’s very old-fashioned, working with photographic films
# 小时候那个是吧
The one in childhood, right?
# 对对 这就是小时候
Yah, in the childhood
# 这个还可以用的吗
Is this still working?
# 可以用可以用
Yeah, it’s still functioning
# 这个就厉害了
This is amazing
# 对 这个挺好的
Yah, it feels good
# 我记得我们小时候那个要挑啊 挑着去学校放
I remember when we were little, it was carried to schools to play films
# 对对对
Yeah
# 然后每个人收一块钱还是五毛钱
And charging everyone 1RMB, or maybe 50 cents
# 这也差不多 以前就是这样
Yeah, that's how it used to work
# 对这个印象很深很深
This is very impressive to me
# 这种全向屏的立体声
This all dimension stereo
# 感觉身临其境 站在你身边的感觉
Feels immersive, like a very close feeling
# 我给你们试一下
Let’s try it
# 这个是实时录的
This is recorded real-time?
# 嗯
Yeah
# 为什么没有风噪
Why is there no wind noise?
# 对 这个就是啊
Yeah, this one
# 一点风噪都没有
No wind noise at all
# 我们现在剪片都是用达芬奇
Our video editing is all done with DaVinci Resolve
# 嗯
Yeah
# 我其实也推荐你们转向达芬奇
I also recommend you switch to DaVinci
# 因为相对来说会更简单 调色调颜色
Because it's relatively easier. Like color mixing
# 处理佳能的东西会更加有优势一点
It has some advantage deal with Cannon stuff
# 佳能相机拍出来的更有优势
Cannon cameras have the edge
# 对 佳能拍出来的会更有优势一点
Yeah, Cannon has a bit more edge
# 然后比如说调色的话
When we talk about color mixing
# 调色的话就是比如说这边可以red的话它最大的优势
And that’s the biggest advantage of Red
# 就是它可以后期转成ut 后期转成ut就行
You can convert it into UT during post-production work
# 然后比如说我们可以套一个lut 就是调色的lut
For example, we can use the lookup table when we are doing color mixing
# 然后现在可以给你调出这种感觉
And now you can have this feeling
# 这个质感是完全是无法比拟的
The image quality is extradentary
# 然后我们就到时候有任何问题问我就行了
And you can ask me any question you have later
# 有什么问题尽管问
Just ask me if you have any questions
# 我们到时候拉个群 我们可以拉个群到时有问题（就问） 简单 这个好办
We can create a group chat, and let me know any question you have, It’s simple
# 今天太耽误您时间了
I have taken too much time of you today
# 没有没有
Nah
# 行了今天差不多
Alright, that’s about it
# 行行行 多谢多谢
Okay, thank you so much
# 欢迎欢迎 特地跑这么远过来
You are welcome, you came all the way here
# 行了行了
Ok ok
# 好 沺沺 我们准备回去了
Alright, Tiantian, we are heading back now